Finding Aid for the Horace Tapscott Papers PASC-M.0237
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Sound Recordings, Series 1.
  - Assorted Identified Sound Recordings, Subseries 1.
    - Concert at the Great House, 1976 March 20; 2 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Personnel: Herbert Callies, acl; Jesse Sharps, ss; Ernest, ts; Michael Sessions, as; Adele, flute and vocals; Aubrey Hart, fl; Amos Delone, bari; Al Hines, b; David B., Ishmael Balaka, perc, congas; Bill Madison, drums, perc; Werevu Isheguru, perc, Wendell Williams, fr horn; Horace Tapscott piano. Compositions: Along the Nile -- Half and Half -- Eternal Egypt -- Little Boy Why are you crying? / Samuel Brown) -- Black Woman I love you (Kamau and Nate Morgan) -- Quagmire 5 am -- the Goat and the Ram Jam -- Buckwheat and syrup (that's Michael and Adele) -- Ole.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), 1976 May 8 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Los Angeles Juvenile Hall. Personnel: Jesse Sharps, Kenyatta, David B., Bob Crowley, Adele, Arthur Wells, Aubrey Hart, Michael Session, Charles Chandler, Fuasi, James Andrews, Herbert Callies, Bill Madison, Ishmael Balaka, Marla Gibbs.
    - Tape of radio advertisement, 09/11/1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      For actor/writer Clarence Muse
    - Radio Advertisement, 09/11/1976 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      Tape of radio advertisement for actor/writer Clarence Muse
    - Concert at the Sea by PAPA, 1976 October 11; 1 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott and Marla Gibbs. Compositions: The Call -- The Goat and the Ram Jam -- Ole -- monologue -- Lester's Solo from Milestones -- Desert Fairy Princess.
    - Concert at the Sea by PAPA, 1976 October 11; 2 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Concert at the Sea by PAPA, 1976 October 11; 3 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Valley College, 1976 November 12 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Compositions: Mike's Tune -- Sweet Jesus (from Sweet Jesus, Preacher Man, which became Aieee, the Phantom) / H. Tapscott -- Giant Steps -- Little Africa -- Kinjie's Dance -- Umatu / Michael Session -- Departure.
      Personnel includes: Horace Tapscott; James Andrews; Steve Smith; Aubrey Hart; Amos de Lone; Linda Hill; Jesse Sharps; Lester Robertson; Kamonta Polk; Arthur Wells; Robert Crowley; Michael Session; Kafi; Jean; David Bryant, Conga; Mike; Bill Madison, drums; Jimmy Hoskins; Ismael; (note: Adele is the hospital). Tape 1 of 2.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Valley College, 1976 November 12 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Compositions include: Mike's Tune -- Sweet Jesus (from Sweet Jesus, Preacher Man, which became Aieee, the Phantom) / H. Tapscott -- Giant Steps -- Little Africa -- Kinjie's Dance -- Umatu / Michael Session -- Departure.
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; James Andrews; Steve Smith; Aubrey Hart; Amos de Lone; Linda Hill; Jesse Sharps; Lester Robertson; Kamonta Polk; Arthur Wells; Robert Crowley; Michael Session; Kafi; Jean; David Bryant, Conga; Mike, Bill Madison, Jimmy Hoskins, Ismael (note: Adele is the hospital). Tape 2 of 2.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in Concert at the IUCC, 1976 November 28 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      Compositions: Masters at Work / E.Straughter -- the Gathering / E.Straughter -- Evening Last Sun Rays / Cerion Middleton -- Kinjie's Dance / Michael S. -- Crepuscule for Nelli / Monk -- Sweet Jesus -- Black Anthem -- Effie.
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Adele Sebastian; Aubrey Hart; Michael Session; Arthur Wells, alto session; James Andrews, tenor; Amos, baritone saxophone; Steve Smith, trumpet; Wendell Williams, french horn; Lester Robertson; Herbert Callies, acl; Jesse Sharps, soprano saxophone; Ismael Balaka, drums; David Bryant, Kamonta, Eugene Ruffins, bass, Jimmy Hoskins, perc, drums; Linda Hill, voice; Robert Crowley, piano; Bill Madison, drums, Dett and Chaga, engrs. Tape 2 of 2.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in Concert at the IUCC, 1976 November 28 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Compositions include: Masters at Work / E.Straughter -- the Gathering / E.Straughter -- Evening Last Sun Rays / Cerion Middleton -- Kinjie's Dance / Michael S. -- Crepuscule for Nelli / Monk -- Sweet Jesus -- Black Anthem -- Effie.
      Personnel includes: Horace Tapscott; Adele Sebastian; Aubrey Hart; Michael Session; Arthur Wells, alto saxophone; James Andrews, tenor; Amos, baritone saxophone; Steve Smith, trumpet; Wendell Williams, french horn; Lester Robertson; Herbert Callies, acl; Jesse Sharps, soprano saxophone; Ismael Balaka, drums; David Bryant, Kamonta, Eugene Ruffins, bass; Jimmy Hoskins, perc, drums; Linda Hill, voice; Robert Crowley, piano; Bill Madison, drums; Dett and Chaga, engrs. Tape 1 of 2.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Central City, 1976 December 26 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1976 April 25 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Duke Ellington Birthday Party Concert.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Malcolm X Festival, Val Verde Park, 1976 May 16 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Compositions include: Desert Fairy Princess -- Little Africa -- Departure -- Black National Anthem -- Eternal Egypt.
      Personnel includes: Horace Tapscott; Jesse; Michael; Steve; Fuasi; Ishmael; Bill; Amos; Arthur; Bob; Kamau; Michael; Charles; Chaga; David; Wendell; James; Adele.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in Concert at Martin L. King Park, 1976 May 30 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Festival in Black Pomona. Compositions: Half & Half -- Desert Fairy -- Mike's Tune -- Ancestral Echoes -- Quagmire Manor, 5am.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Last Sunday Concert at the IUCC, 1976 May 31 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Compositions: Making out (chant, McCoy, Tyner), Herbie Baker Medley, Flight 17, Little A's Chant, Prance Dance, Interlude,'Inspirations of silence ( E. Straughter), Little Boy why are you crying?, Living Room (Max Roach), Haunted (Maxine Swan), Freedom. (Stanley "Chico" Robertson, who is an audience), Half & Half ( Charles Davis).
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1976 June 27 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Compositions: Goat and Ram Jam -- Hight Priest / McCoy Tyner -- Ole / Coltrane -- Flight 17 -- Golden Pearl.
      Personnel includes: Adele Sebastian, flute; Michael Session; Fuasi; Charles Chandler; James Andrews; Steve Smith, trumpet; Amos de Lone; Herbert Callies; Kamau T. Shams wa Kamra (aka Kamau Daaood); Lester Robertson, trombone; Watt; Horace Tapscott; David Bryant; Bill Madison, drums; Ismael Balaka; Mike Daniel; Jesse, Chaga, engineers.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in concert at Widney High School, 1976 July 25 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Last Sunday Concert. Compositions include: Goat and Ram -- flight 17 -- Ole -- Mode for John -- Little A's Chant -- the Meeting / Elaine Brown -- Sandy and Niles.
      Personnel: Adele Sebastian; Aubrey Hart; Arthur, flutes; Michael Session, alto saxophone; Fuasi; Semaj and Charles, tenor saxophone; Amos, baritone saxophone; Herbert C., alto clarinet; Steve Smith, trumpet; Lester Robertson, trombone; Wendell and Bob Watt, french horns; Horace Tapscott; David Bryant, bass; Bill Madison and Ismael Balaka, drums; Conga Mike, congas; Linda, vocal, Jesse Sharps, soprano saxophone; Chaga, engineers.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Last Sunday of the Month Concert, 1976 August 29 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Widneys HS, 4 pm. Compositions include: Jitterbug Waltz -- Inspirations of Silence -- the Call -- Mike's Tune -- Flashback in Time -- Half and Half -- It's Time / Max Roach.
      Personnel includes: Adele; Arthur; Kafi, flutes; David Bryant; Bob Crowley, piano; Ishmael and Bill Madison, drums; Werevu Isigubu, congas; Jesse, soprano saxophone; Michael Session, alto saxophone; Herbert Callies, acl; Fuasi; Charles Chandler; James Andrews, tenor saxophone; Amos, baritone saxophone; Wendell Williams, french horn; Chaga; Michael Clark and Craig Hutton.
      Photographes for UGMAA.
    - Last Sunday IUCC Concert, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Compositions: Little A's chant, Warriors Mate
    - Passing Through, 1977; 3.5" open reel audio tape (Box 75)
      Passing Through (music from film?) L. Clark, T. Lange,
      The "Call" Lester Robertson
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), ARK at Inner City Cultural, 1977 January 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1977 January 30 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Compositions: The Back Beat / Horace Silver -- Little Boy, Why are you crying? -- Desert Fairy Princess -- March U A. Africa / Charles Chandler -- Kinjie's Dance / Michael Session -- Quagmire Minor at 5pm / Session -- Black Anthem (last two on Mark Weber disc..).
      Personnel includes: Adele; Jesse, soprano saxophone; David Bryant; Linda Hill, piano and vocals; Steve Smith, trumpet; Ishmael Balaka, drums; Michael Daniel, congas; Bill Madison, drums; Lester Robertson; Kamau T.Shams Wa Kamra; Michael Session, alto saxophone; Charles Boyd Chandler, tenor s; Horatio Tapscott; perhaps James Andrews.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at UC Riverside, 1977 February 11 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Black Student Union Presentation, Black History Month Activity.
      Personnel includes: Adele; Jesse; Arthur Wells; Michael Session; Charles Chandler; James Andrews; Amos; David Bryant; Kamonta; Eugene Ruffin; Ishmael Balaka; Lester Robertson; Bobby West; Linda Hills; Marla Gibbs; Horace Tapscott; Chaga; engr.; Jackie Simpson; Kamau.
    - No location, 02/26/1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Personnel: Arthur Blythe, Alto; Ahmed Abdullah, Trumpet; Bob Stewart, tuba; Abdul Wadud, cello; Steve Reid, drums; Muhamad Abdullah, percussions
      Compositions by A.B. The Grip, Spirit in the Field, Sunrise Service, Lower Nile, As of Yet, My son RA.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), last Sunday concert at the IUCC, 1977 February 27 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Compositions: In chant-meant / Charles Chandler -- Song for Shawishi / James Andrews -- Mike's Tune -- I Felt Spring / E.Straughter -- Giant Steps.
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Adele; Arthur Wells; Kafi; Michael Session, alto sax; Jesse, soprano sax; James Andrews,tenor; Charles Chandler, tenor saxophone; Amos, baritone saxophone; Steve Smith, trumpet; Bill Madison, drums; Ishmael Balaka, drums; David Bryant; Kamonta; Linda Hill; Chaga- Jihad Masai- Yasin, engr.
    - UGMAA Foundation, Marla Gibbs at Bovard Auditorium, 1977 March 7; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 72, Folder 17)
      USC?
      Personnel includes: Horace Tapscott; Jesse Sharps; David Bryant; Bill Madison; Watts Symphony Orchestra, cond. by Octace Bonomo.
    - UGMAA Foundation Presents Songs for the Unsung, 1977 May 8; Tape 1of 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Doug Weston's Troubadour, Mother's Day Concert-"Day of the Tornado in Long Beach"/Sonny Criss in Concert.
      Peronnel: the Pan People Arkestra
      Composition: Thoughts of Dar es- Salaam
      Composed and conducted by Horace Tapscott,3/7 pm(Flyer enclosed..)
    - Concert Series: Songs for the Unsung. Pt. 2. #5877, 1977 May 8; Tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Radio Interview: "Profiles in Jazz." Gary Vercelli, interviewer; Horace Tapscott, interviewee. KCRW FM 89.9 Santa Monica, Calif. "Radio Free Jazz." CS #5177. Recorded in 04/25/1977.
      Compositions: Illusions -- Right Out That Window. CS# 5877. Recorded in New York in 1975.
      Black Arthur Blythe Quartet. Personnel includes: Black Arthur, alto sax; Les Walker, piano; Steve Reid, drums; Ken Hudson, bass.
    - The ARK at Irvine:, 1977 May 14 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Campus Park Picnic Concert
      Personnel: Adele Sebastien; James Andrews; Michael Session; Charles Chandler; Linda Hill; Amos de Lone; Arthur Wells; Kafi Laurence; Kmonte Laurence Polk; Ishmael Balaka; Wiliam Madison; David Bryant; Bobby West; Steven Smith; Jesse Sharps.
      Horace Tapscott: ARK conductor
      Clarice: recorder:pres + res
      CHAGA: audio recorder
      Michael D. Wilcots pres.+ res HOLLY CAYNES Sec
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at UCLA, Schoenberg Hall., 1977 May 21 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Compositions: Peyote -- Parker's Mood -- It's Time.
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Jesse; Dadisi Wells; Aubrey Hart; James Andrews, tenor saxophone; Kafi; Amos; Linda, Bill Madison, drums; David Bryant.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Voters Rally Concert, 1977 May 29 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Councilman Farrell's rally for voters at 3725 Don Felipe Dr.
      Personnel includes: Jesse Sharps; James Andrews; David Bryant; Marla; Aubrey Hart; Bill Madison; Horace Tapscott. Notes: present were Mayor Tom Bradley, Councilmen Gilbert Lindsay, David Cunningham, Robert Farrell.
    - NEH grant demo tape, Spring 1977 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; David Bryant
      Compositions: Come Sunday (Duke Ellington) Moon Rays
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Watts Towers, 1977 July 9 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      Compositions include: Bakai -- Oriental Flower -- Mike's Tune -- Equinox -- Departure.
      Personnel includes: Jesse; Ray Draper, tuba; Aubrey Hart; Herbert Callies, alto clarinet; Bill Madison; Horace Tapscott; James Andrews; Kafi; David B; Linda Hill, vocal.
    - Les, 08/28/1977; 1 of 2 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Jesse; Ray Draper, tuba; Lester; Aubrey Hart; James Andrews, tenor sax; Wendell Williams, french horn; Linda Hill, piano and vocals; Kamau T. Shams, word musician (on Mothership); David B.; Herbert Callies, alto clarinet; Sabir Mateen, tenor sax
      Compositions: Les (Eric Dolphy for Lester Robertson, arr. by Jesse Sharps), In Times Like These (Lester Roberts), Sketches of Drunken Mary, Dream Nigguh(Linda Hill)
    - Mothership, 08/28/1977; 2 of 2 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Compositions: Mothership (Be There), Effendi (McCoy Tyner), Black National Anthem, Effi
    - Studio mixes for "oh! Happy Day", 09/22/1977 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Lester Young Interview, 11/10/1977 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Black Arthur, 1977 November 25 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Century Playhouse Concert, 1977 December 4; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 34)
      Compositions: Warriors All / H. Tapscott -- The Call / Lester R. -- Sea Wife / Jesse Sharps -- Mike's Tune / Jesse Sharps -- Lush Life -- In times like these -- (Lester), Mothership -- Bakai / Cal Massey.
      Personnel: Jesse, Herbert Callies, Bill Madison, James Andrews, Kafi Roberts, Kamonta, Sabir Mateen, David Bryant, Nate Morgan, Horace Tapscott.
    - Century Playhouse Concert, 1977 December 4; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 35)
      Compositions: Lately's Solo (HT'S arrangement of Lester's solo on Milestone recorded with Gerald Wilson's Band) -- Departure.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1977 December 25; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 75)
      Tape 1 of 3. Michael Dett: sometimes the Rev would ask Ark to perform earlier in the day as part of the church services.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1977 December 25; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 75)
      Tape 2 of 3. Michael Dett: sometimes the Rev would ask Ark to perform earlier in the day as part of the church services.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1977 December 25; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 75)
      Tape 3 of 3. Michael Dett: sometimes the Rev would ask Ark to perform earlier in the day as part of the church services.
    - Kwanzaa Celebration at Centinela Park, 12/31/1977 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Kafi; Michael S; Jesse; Lester; James Andrews, tenor sax and bass clarinet; Sabir Mateen, tenor sax, etc.
      Compositions: Goat and the Ram Jam, As of Yet (A. Blythe)
    - UGMAA highlights tape, 01/25/1978 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, David B>, Linda, vocal.
      Compositions: Me and Dee; Spellbound (Clifford Jordan), Faitsha (Will Connell Jr.), Little Africa, Snady and Niles.
      Exc.: Ancestral Echoes (in 4 parts: Songs of Songhay), Transplantation, Songs of the New world, Echo theme), Horace Tapscott, piano, Octave Bonomo, conductor, David B., Bill Madison, Jesse S., Wooden Flute, Watts Symphony Orchestra (75 pieces)
    - UGMAA Highlights tape, 1978 January 25; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 75)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; David B; Linda, vocalist. Compositions: Me and Dee, Spellbound (Clifford Jordan), Faitsha (Will Conell Jr.), Little Africa, Sandy and Niles.
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, piano; Octave Bonomo, conductor; David B., Bill Madison, Jesse S., Wooden flute. Compositions: Ancestral Echoes (in 4 parts: Songs of Songhay, Transplantation, Songs of the New World, Echo theme)
      Watts Symphony Orchestra (75 pieces).
    - UGMAA ARKives, 1978 February 10; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 36)
      Personnel: David Bryant, bass; Everett Brown Jr., drums; Arthur Blythe, alto sax; Walter Savage, bass; Horace Tapscott, piano.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at UCLA, 1978 February 17 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Black history Month. Compositions: Macrame / Jesse Sharps -- Steam / Zeke Cooper -- Mawi (sp?, Kamonta) -- Dial "B" for Barbra / H. Tapscott.
    - Song of the Unsung, 1978 February 18; 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, piano. Compositions: Songs of the Unsung -- Blue Essence -- Bakai -- In Times Like These.
    - Songs of the Unsung, 1978 February 18; 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, piano. Compositions: Mary On Sunday -- Lush Life -- The Goat and Ram Jam -- Something For Kenny.
    - The Call: Horatio #1 take, 03/12/1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - The Call: Clarisse #2 take, 03/12/1978 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Maui, 03/12/1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Quagmirer Manor, 03/12/1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Quagmirer Manor at 5:00 am #1 take
    - Quagmirer Manor, 03/12/1978 (Box 14)
      Quagmirer Manor at 5:00 am #2 take
    - Nakatini, 03/25/1978; 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Compositions: Nakatini Suite,(Cal Massey)
    - Nakatini Suite, 03/25/1978 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      Compositions: Nakatini Suite (Cal Massey), Peyote Song (Jesse Sharps)
    - Peyote Song #3, 1978 March 25; 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Breeze - Maui, 1978 March 25; 3 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Little Boy why are you crying, 03/25/1978; 4 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Last Sunday of The Month Concert at the IUCC, 03/26/1978 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Compositions: I Felt Spring, (E.Straughter, Impressions of The Ghetto (Horace Tapscott- the suite), Horacio (RMM), Daydreamer (Kamonta Polk), Little Boy why are you crying (Browne), National Anthem.
    - Last Sunday of the Month Concert at the IUCC, 03/26/1978; 2 of 3 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Compositions: I Felt Spring (E. Straughter), Impressions of the Ghetto (HT - the suite?), Horacio (RMM), Daydreamer (Kamonta Polk), LIttle boy why are you crying (Browne), National Anthem
    - Last Sunday of the Month Concert at the IUCC, 03/26/1978; 3 of 3 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Studio Tapes, 04/08/1978; 2 of 4 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Duplicates of the masters for the album (also some used on Flight 17p?).
      Compositions: Nakatini, Peyote Song No. 3
    - Studio Tapes, 04/08/1978; 3 of 4 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      Compositions: Horacio, Maui
    - Studio Tapes, 04/08/1978; 4 of 4 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Compositions: The Call, Quagmire
    - Studio Tapes, 04/08/1978; 1 of 4 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Compositions: Flight 17, Breeze
    - PAPA sessions for the album, "The Call", 04/08/1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, bandleader, soprano saxaphone, tenor saxaphone, bamboo flute; Linda, piano; Adele, vocals, flute; Lester; David B; Everett; Herbert Callies, alto clarinet; James Andrews, tenor saxaphone, bass clarinet; Michael Session, alto saxaphone; Kafi Roberts, flute, soprano saxaphone; Archie Johnson, trombone; Red Callender, tuba, bass; Bill Madison, percussion, drums; Louis Spears, cello, bass; Kamonta Polk, bass
      Compositions: Nakatini, Peyote Song #3
    - Master for The Call, 04/18/1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Studio Copies, 04/18/1978 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Compositions: Clarice, Little Boy, Your Child
    - Macrame, 02/25/1979 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      PAPA at the IUCC Compositions: Macrame, Dial "B" for Barbra
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 March 25; 1 of 4 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Compositions: Village Dance.
      Personnel: Billie Harris; Manual Billups, french horn; Sabir Mateen; Jon Williams, baritone sax; Aubrey Hart; Adele Sebastian; Al Hines; David Bryant; Daaood Woods, congas; Everett Brown, Jr., drums; Horace Tapscott.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 March 25 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      Compositions: Mykoseky's 1st Fifth / Jesse Sharps (Mykosesky is Michael Clark, The Photographer).
      Personnel: Billie Harris; Manual Billups, french horn; Sabir Mateen; Jon Williams, baritone sax; Aubrey Hart; Adele Sebastian; Al Hines; David Bryant; Daaood Woods, congas; Everett Brown, Jr., drums; Horace Tapscott. Tape 2 of 4.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 March 25 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      Compositions: Dee Bee's Dance -- Desert Fairy Princess -- Lush Life.
      Personnel: Billie Harris; Manual Billups, french horn; Sabir Mateen; Jon Williams, baritone sax; Aubrey Hart; Adele Sebastian; Al Hines; David Bryant; Daaood Woods, congas; Everett Brown, Jr., drums; Horace Tapscott. Tape 3 of 4.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 March 25 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      Compositions: Sea Wife / Jesse Sharps -- Black National Anthem.
      Personnel: Billie Harris; Manual Billups, french horn; Sabir Mateen; Jon Williams, baritone sax; Aubrey Hart; Adele Sebastian; Al Hines; David Bryant; Daaood Woods, congas; Everett Brown, Jr., drums; Horace Tapscott. Tape 4 of 4.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 April 29 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Compositions: Village Dance / Sabir Mateen -- Song of Emanon / H. Tapscott -- Sea Wife -- Dee Bee's Dance / H. Tapscott -- Mykoseky's 1st Fifth -- C-Jam Blues -- Mood Indigo -- Sophisticated Lady -- Satin Doll -- Caravan -- Lift Every Voice -- Village Dance.
      Personnel: Billie Harris; Manuel Billups, french horn; Sabir Mateen; Jon Williams, baritone saxophone; Aubrey Hart; Adele Sebastian; Al Hines; David Bryant; Daaood Woods, congas; Everett Brown, Jr., drums; Horatio Tapscott. Note: Bruce Bidback and Tom Albach are there, probably recording; tapes are high quality. 2 tapes of part 1.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 April 29 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Compositions include: Village Dance / Sabir Mateen -- Song of Emanon / H. Tapscott -- Sea Wife, Dee Bee's Dance / H. Tapscott -- Mykoseky's 1st Fifth -- C-Jam Blues -- Mood Indigo -- Sophisticated Lady -- Satin Doll -- Caravan -- Lift Every Voice -- Village Dance.
      Personnel includes: Billie Harris; Manuel Billups, french horn; Sabir Mateen; Jon Williams, baritone saxophone; Aubrey Hart; Adele Sebastian; Al Hines; David Bryant; Daaood Woods, congas; Everett Brown, Jr., drums; Horatio Tapscott. Note: Bruce Bidback and Tom Albach are there, probably recording; tapes are high quality. second tape of part 1.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 May 27 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Compositions: Village Dance -- Future Sally 's Time / A. Blythe and S. Crouch -- Many Nights Ago / Carmel Crunk -- Sea Wife -- L.T.T. / H. Tapscott -- Village Dance -- Lift Every Voice.